lifeintwo.com 2019-05-10

# Life in Two

Privacy

## Article 1. Protection of privacy and treatment of personal dataRead >>

LIFEINTWO respectes the European, Spanish and Swiss laws in force regarding the protection of privacy and personal data processing. Some information, signs or content (photographs or personal information) that Members can enter, under their own responsibility, might reveal their racial and ethnic origin, religious or philosophical beliefs, political opinions, membership to political parties, trade unions, religious, philosophical, political, trade union associations or organizations as well as personal information such as their health conditions or sexual life. By entering such optional information at their own free will, the Member expresses consent to LIFEINTWO to process such "sensitive" data and takes the whole responsibility.  
Furthermore, all the collected personal information (including, by way of example and not limited to: email address, telephone and mobile number, text ads, user's interests and how the user uses the Service), will be used both for internal communications, regarding the services offered by LIFEINTWO for commercial communications, and marketing communications by LIFEINTWO’s partner companies.

Members can send an e-mail to [www.help-tkd.com/](http://www.help-tkd.com/en_GB/contact/index/pid/21) for matters concerning privacy protection. The user must specify his/her nickname, password and e-mail address to access or request access to information about him/her, to make changes, delete it or prohibit LIFEINTWO from using it in a certain way, following the directions given in article 1.5 ("Person in charge of the personal data processing of") During sign-up or at a subsequent moment at LIFEINTWO site, Members can request to receive and, later on, freely ask to not receive anymore the LIFEINTWO newsletter and/or promotional offers sent by LIFEINTWO and/or its partners by email and/or to their mobile phone. 

## 1.1. Type of the information collectedRead >>

The personal information gathered by LIFEINTWO may include email addresses, landline and/or mobile telephone numbers, information about one's physical aspect, photographs, personal ads, user's interests and how users enjoy the Service.   
Furthermore, some non-personal information can be collected, such as the browser version (Internet Explorer, Mozilla, etc.), operating system used by the user (Windows 98, Mac OS, etc) and the IP address of the computer used. LIFEINTWO can use cookies whose purpose is to save the Member's identification information while visiting LIFEINTWO, to prevent the Member from having to enter them manually for every page visited. Members can prevent the use of cookies any time they want by changing their Internet browser options.  
By sending or entering any personal information at LIFEINTWO site, the user accepts the methods and purposes of the processing and expresses his/her consent for their use according to the provisions of this article.  
LIFEINTWO gathers personal information sent voluntarily by its users at the LIFEINTWO web site and binds itself not to divulge the personal information in any way. 

During the sign-up procedure to join LIFEINTWO network, one's nicknames, email addresses, sex, birthdate and telephone numbers are saved.  
If further personal information is saved in the profile, LIFEINTWO collects that information as well.   
If personal information is entered using one of the functions of LIFEINTWO network, that information is stored under the file ("published information").  
If the user contacts LIFEINTWO by email, the email address and the information contained in the message will be stored.

After signing up for LIFEINTWO and accessing the services, the user is no longer anonymous. If someone visits the Website without signing up for LIFEINTWO, that user will be anonymous. If further information will be available in the personal Information section, it will be also collected using adequate technology.

This website uses Google Analytics, a service of web analysis provided by Google, Inc. ("Google"). Google Analytics uses some "cookies", which are text files stored in your computer, to allow the website, analyze how users use the website. The outcome of these cookies, on how the website is used by you (including your IP address), will be transmitted and stored at the US Google server. Google will use this information to track and examine your website usage, fill in reports on the website activity for the website's operators and supply other services related to the website's activity and to the Internet usage. Google may transmit this information to third parties, where required by the law, or in case these third parties treat the data on behalf of Google. Google will never link your IP address to any other data owned by Google. You may refuse to use the cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, but this might prevent you from using all the features of this website. By using this website, you agree to your data being processed by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above. 

## 1.2. Contents divulgated by the MembersRead >>

Members bear the exclusive responsibility regarding the contents, such as, pictures, profiles, messages published or broadcast at LIFEINTWO site. By publishing or broadcasting such content at LIFEINTWO site, members authorize LIFEINTWO expressly to reproduce, represent, adapt, translate, convert into digital format, extract completely or partially such content for any advertisement, marketing or any other purpose, to grant or authorize subcontracts, at LIFEINTWO site or any other partner channel of the site, on any support or by any broadcasting means, especially digital means (email, SMS, Internet, CD-Rom or DVD-Rom) or audio-visual communication (press, radio, terrestrial, digital, cable or satellite television.) The Member expressly authorizes LIFEINTWO to change the above-mentioned content in order to render it compliant with the graphic aspect of LIFEINTWO site or other communication supports mentioned above and/or to make them compatible with the corresponding technical services or formats of the supports involved. The Member cannot copy, reproduce or use the content regarding other Members in any way, unless it is strictly related to Services use for personal and private purposes.  
Members and/or users are banned from publishing or broadcasting content that may violate third-party's intellectual property rights at the site or through LIFEINTWO's services by any means.

## 1.3. Who can access that informationRead >>

Personal data is processed exclusively electronically and is handled using a computer-based authentication system. User's information is archived on protected databases and can be accessed only by those in charge of handling them and in case of necessity only.  
Personal information provided by the user during sign-up, which is not a part of his/her personal ads or of his/her presentation, is not accessible to third parties; nor will it be transmitted, sold or exchanged, except for the below mentioned cases only after having informed and received the user's consent or in case the user has not expressed any objection with its regards.   
During sign-up, the user expresses his/her consent to communicate his/her data to LIFEINTWO's partners for marketing or commerical purposes. In case the user doesn't want to receive any longer offers selected for him/her by LIFEINTWO or from its partners, he/she can terminate his/her subscription at any time, also at a future moment, in his/her personal profile under the section: my account/email services.   
Sometimes LIFEINTWO can give general, social-demographic information to some of its partners anonymously to conduct statistical studies and/or promotional surveys (for age groups, sex, etc). In those cases, it is not sent any information that could be used to identify individual users.  
Contents published by members in their personal ads, search criteria and presentation are accessible at LIFEINTWO site and by email (newsletter). Furthermore, this information can be broadcasted by LIFEINTWO or LIFEINTWO's partners through the newsletters, other web sites, any electronic means of communication (email, SMS, etc), by audio-visual means (radio, television, etc.) or press (newspapers, magazines, etc).

Please refer to the provisions of art. 5 "Intellectual property" for anything related to contents intellectual property rights. Members have the right to delete such content from the site at any time by terminating their contract with LIFEINTWO, according to the provisions of art. 5 of the terms and conditions: "Termination of contract and profile removal". Since it concerns information available in the announcement, in the research criteria and in the Member's presentation, the data will be definitively deleted only after the next update or after the next modification of the communication means (printed, audiovisual or digital) which include the Member's contents.   
Pursuant to applicable law on data protection in the European Economic Area (EEA), the data controller of the website is LIFEINTWO TEKKA DIGITAL SA based in Balestra 12, 6900 Lugano, Switzerland (fax: +41 91 604 6487)  
The member expressly authorizes TEKKA DIGITAL SA to transfer the information provided to LIFEINTWO and the above mentioned rights and benefits to LIFEINTWO's partners and successors.

## 1.4. Purpose of data processingRead >>

LIFEINTWO gathers information and data in different ways and at various occasions. Some personal information is gathered when you sign up to join LIFEINTWO, other information is gathered while you are using LIFEINTWO services or when you participate in any other program of it, which allows you to enjoy services in a customized way and participate in various initiatives raised by LIFEINTWO. This information allows us to adapt the service or the site to the Member's needs and sent them information, offers, promotional messages about the services and products that might be of his/her interest. The Member will receive this information if and only he/she has expressed interest therein. The Member can revoke his/her consent at any time, by changing his/her LIFEINTWO personal settings.  
Furthermore, LIFEINTWO processes Members' information for the following purposes, in order to offer its services and manage different ways of payment, including charging for goods or services purchased on line: for purposes arising from the obligations foreseen by Swiss and European Union laws, regulations and norms as well as directions given by competent Authorities (for example: investigations of the public prosecutor or law-enforcement agencies, accounting and fiscal logging, etc.); to comply with contractual obligations, technical support and information, after sales assistance. In order to bill/charge the due amounts, for the order fulfillment process and for any other need that involves other subjects (such as mailing of postal communications).

## 1.5. Person in charge of the data processingRead >>

The person in charge of Processing is TEKKA DIGITAL SA company, the provider of LIFEINTWO service, headquartered in Via Balestra 12, 6900 Lugano, Switzerland (fax: +41 91 604 6487). The data and www.LIFEINTWO.com site are protected at the headquarters of the Person in charge of the data processing.  
The Member can contact at any time, by sending an email to the [Support](http://www.help-tkd.com/en_GB/contact/index/pid/21), to the Person in charge of data processing, in order to obtain a confirmation whether there exists personal data related to him/her, even if he/she has not signed up to become a member yet and have them communicated in an intelligible way.  
Furthermore, the Member has the right to ask the Person in charge of Personal Data Processing to delete his/her personal data (by that, it is means to destroy such information without any possibility to restore it), transform it into anonymous form (changing the data into anonymous format) or to freeze the treatment of their personal data (conserving the data by temporarily suspending any kind of processing.)   
The Member has the right to object to the processing of any personal data concerning him/her, in whole or partly, on legitimate grounds, even if they are relevant to the purpose of the collection, or they can object to the processing of personal data concerning him/her to send advertisement, direct sales, conduct market research or commercial communication.

## 1.6. Cookie PolicyRead >>

The site uses the cookies to identify you as a member of this Site, to remember your favorite language and to facilitate your surfing on the Site. It is possible to disable the cookies in your own Internet browser, but, by doing so, some parts of the Site won't work correctly  
To learn more about the cookies, including flash cookies and technologies of local sorage, we suggest you to check the following sites: 

  * [helpx.adobe.com/flash-player/kb/disable-local-shared-objects-flash.html](http://helpx.adobe.com/flash-player/kb/disable-local-shared-objects-flash.html)

The site uses Google Analytics to gather data on who's viewed the site. This information is used to draft reports and to improve the site itself. The cookies gather some type of data, in a complete anonymous way, such as the number of site visits, the visitors' origin and the viewed pages. For further information on the privacy Policy of Google, please visit [www.google.com/intl/en/policies/](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/)
